Corrupt binary codes infecting my mind
손상된 이진코드는 내 마음을 감염시켜
意識に侵食してくる 崩れた0と1
錯亂的0和1侵蝕著意識
错乱的0和1侵袭着意识
Perform invocation with numbing freeze
차갑고 무감각하게 호출을 수행하고 있어
感情のないまま 執行される喚起の命令
麻木冰冷地執行調用
麻木冰冷地执行调用
Querying for a variable and seizing the time
하나의 변수를 질의하고 시간을 붙잡아
因果の変数を掴み その瞬間を止める
查詢一個變數並綁定時間
查询一个变量并绑定时间
To recompile and trigger my destiny
다시 컴파일하고 운명의 방아쇠를 당기네
修正実行 運命を再起動する
去重新編譯、觸發命運
去重新编译 触发命运
Though my wings've been bloodstained and could never rid
비록 내 날개가 피에 얼룩져 지워지지 않더라도
汚れた血が滲んだこの翼でも
即使雙翼早已濺上無法擺脫的血污
即使双翼早已溅上无法摆脱的血污
I'll try hard to soar to the heaven I dreamed
꿈꾸던 천국을 향해 전력으로 날아오를 거야
ネバーランドを求めて 強く羽ばたく
為了夢中彼岸，我要全力飛翔
为了梦中的彼岸 我要全力飞翔
There is no "exception" in this library
나의 라이브러리에는 "예외"란 존재하지 않아
私のライブラリに もうエラーは発生しないよ
這個庫不會報出“異常”
这个库中不会报出“异常”
For I know I will always go with you
항상 너와 함께할 거라는 걸 나는 아니까
君について行くと決めたから
因為我知道，我永遠會與你同行
因为我知道 我会永远与你同行
Superhot projectiles pierce the wind
작열하는 탄두가 바람을 가르고
灼熱の弾丸が風を切り裂く
熾熱的彈頭撕裂疾風
炽热的弹头撕裂疾风
I charged up my armor into lightspeed
가갑을 빛의 속도가 날 때까지 충전시켜
フルチャージした装甲で 光のように疾り出し
我為戰甲增能，直至飛馳如光
我为战甲充能 直至飞驰如光
Querying for a variable and seizing the time
하나의 변수를 질의하고 시간을 붙잡아
因果の変数を掴み その瞬間を止める
查詢一個變數並綁定時間
查询一个变量并绑定时间
In a new day coming not so far away
새롭고도 멀지 않은 미래에서
今にも手が届きそうな 新しい未来を
在全新而並不遙遠的未來
在全新而并不遥远的未来
Though my wings've been bloodstained and could never rid
비록 내 날개가 피에 얼룩져 지워지지 않더라도
汚れた血が滲んだこの翼でも
即使雙翼早已濺上無法擺脫的血污
即使双翼早已溅上无法摆脱的血污
I'll try hard to soar to the heaven I dreamed
꿈꾸던 천국을 향해 전력으로 날아오를 거야
ネンバーランドを求めて 強く羽ばたく
為了夢中彼岸，我要全力飛翔
为了梦中的彼岸 我要全力飞翔
There is no "exception" in this library
나의 라이브러리에는 "예외"란 존재하지 않아
私のライブラリに もうエラーは発生しないよ
這個庫不會報出“異常”
这个库中不会报出“异常”
For I know I will always go with you
항상 너와 함께할 거라는 걸 나는 아니까
君について行くと決めたから
因為我知道，我永遠會與你同行
因为我知道 我会永远与你同行
Though my wings've been bloodstained and could never rid
비록 내 날개가 피에 얼룩져 지워지지 않더라도
汚れた血が滲んだこの翼でも
即使雙翼早已濺上無法擺脫的血污
即使双翼早已溅上无法摆脱的血污
I'll try hard to soar to the heaven I dreamed
꿈꾸던 천국을 향해 전력으로 날아오를 거야
ネンバーランドを求めて 強く羽ばたく
為了夢中彼岸，我要全力飛翔
为了梦中的彼岸 我要全力飞翔
There is no "exception" in this library
나의 라이브러리에는 "예외"란 존재하지 않아
私のライブラリに もうエラーは発生しないよ
這個庫不會報出“異常”
这个库中不会报出“异常”
for I know I will always go with you
항상 너와 함께할 거라는 걸 나는 아니까
君について行くと決めたから
因為我知道，我永遠會與你同行
因为我知道 我会永远与你同行
Though my wings've been bloodstained and could never rid
비록 내 날개가 피에 얼룩져 지워지지 않더라도
汚れた血が滲んだこの翼でも
即使雙翼早已濺上無法擺脫的血污
即使双翼早已溅上无法摆脱的血污
I'll try hard to soar to the heaven I dreamed
꿈꾸던 천국을 향해 전력으로 날아오를 거야
ネンバーランドを求めて 強く羽ばたく
為了夢中彼岸，我要全力飛翔
为了梦中的彼岸 我要全力飞翔
There is no "exception" in this library
나의 라이브러리에는 "예외"란 존재하지 않아
私のライブラリに もうエラーは発生しないよ
這個庫不會報出“異常”
这个库中不会报出“异常”
For I know I will always go with my heart
항상 너와 함께할 거라는 걸 나는 아니까
心に委ねると決めたから
因為我知道，我會永遠與心同行
因为我知道 我会永远与心同行